{
    "subject": "resource/Alex_Troup",
    "predicate": "property/nationalteam",
    "object": "resource/Scotland_national_football_team",
    "human_readable": "Alex Troup plays for Scotland national football team.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.976306140422821,
            "question": "In what competitions has Alex Troup played for Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.948249101638794,
            "question": "For which national football team does Alex Troup play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9482160806655884,
            "question": "How long has Alex Troup been playing for the Scotland national team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9328382611274719,
            "question": "Is Alex Troup a well-known player in Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7630431056022644,
            "question": "Has Alex Troup scored any goals for Scotland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7627142071723938,
            "question": "What other teams has Alex Troup played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5657062530517578,
            "question": "What is Alex Troup's position?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5109079480171204,
            "question": "Does Alex Troup have any notable achievements in his football career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4926413297653198,
            "question": "Where was Alex Troup born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48370134830474854,
            "question": "What is Alex Troup's age?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alex Troup plays for Scotland national football team.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3217_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Alex Troup born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3217_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Alex Troup have any notable achievements in his football career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3217_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Alex Troup's position?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3217_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3217_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis response indicates that according to the context information, the triple \"Alex Troup plays for Scotland national football team\" is supported. This can be inferred from various documents where it is mentioned that Alex Troup was a Scottish international left winger who played for Scotland against England in 1920 and again in Ireland in 1921 and 1922, among other appearances."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that supports the statement \"Alex Troup plays for the Scotland national football team.\" Specifically, the document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3217/re-ranker-msmarco/67.txt states: \"Troup was an original touchline terror and would certainly have made more than the four Scottish international and two Scottish League appearances he managed while at Dens had it not been for Rangers\u2019 \u2018Wee Blue Devil\u2019 Alan Morton.\" This confirms that Alex Troup played for the Scotland national football team."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}